It's only been five days
They're almost bigger than Lewes's
Jason
You're my hero
When we make the money
I'll give you a ten percent cut
Boss
I have an idea
We can make even more
Let's hear it
We only have 20,000 frogs now
Walter wants 50,000
If we can get 50,000
We could make millions more
No use talking about it now
It's all Lewes's fault
If Lewes had lent me the money
I would have bought more forest frog babies
Boss
It's not too late
The bigger the forest frogs, the more they are worth
We can buy some inferior forest frogs
Feed them my secret feed for a few days
Within ten days
They'll be just as big as these
Jason
You're a genius
I'll borrow money to buy more frogs now
Daniel
This is our only house
We can't mortgage it
Mom
Just wait
When I get rich
I'll buy you a villa
These frogs have recovered
They're five grams heavier than before
It won't affect the contract with Walter
That's good
Cynthia
I want to build two more pools
To give the frogs more space to grow
Their quality will go up by ten percent
We need more investment again
Yeah
Walter has high standards
We have to do our best
Then let's expand
If we run out of money
We'll figure it out together
I don't know much about this
But I trust you
Go ahead and do what you want
Let's all take a break
Let's eat first
Then back to work
Coming, Mom